晚安 三角形 晚安 正方形
Good night, Triangle. Good night, Square.
谢谢你们让我们看到学习有多么快乐
Thanks for showing us how fun it is to learn.
你能去拿下他们的睡衣 还是我...
Do you want to get their pajamas, or should I...
接下来播出《血腥杂交7: 器官囤积者的崛起》
Next, "Blood Orgy 7: Rise of the Organ Hoarder."
天啊
Oh, my God!
为什么
Why?!
你是丹尼尔·布恩吗
Are you Daniel Boone?
你是谁
Who's asking?
我是来参观下肯塔基州的
I just came to see Kentucky,
全国第五大烟草出产州
the fifth-largest tobacco producer
和第三大产煤州
and the third-largest coal producer in the country.
我感觉身临其境
I feel like I am there.
唯一比儿童剧院更让人痛苦的
The only thing more painful than children's theater
就是我背部的疼痛
is what's going on with my back right now.
你为何不好好服用医生开给你的药
Why can't you take the pills that the doctor gave you
这样你就能享受你儿子的精彩表演了
so that you can enjoy your son's tour de force?
我只需要伸展一下身子
I just need a little stretch.
这年头 有点小毛病医生就给你开药
Doctors give you pills for everything today.
现在我们需要一位志愿者
Now we need a volunteer.
普里契特先生 谢谢你的热情参与
Mr. Pritchett, thank you for your enthusiasm.
什么
What?
我们的一位小演员被他继父绑架了
One of our players has been kidnapped by his stepfather,
但是演出必须进行下去
but the show must go on.
每当一块领土成为新的州 就在国旗上放颗星
Place a star on the flag every time a territory becomes a state.
说真的 但是警方...
Seriously, but do the police --
来点掌声怎么样
How 'bout a round of applause?!
快点 观众快要失去兴趣了
Faster, please. We're losing them.
你在哪儿呢
Where are you?
你要错过乔的《美国团结50州》演出了
You're missing Joe's tribute to the 50 nifty United States.
我在家躺在床上呢 重感冒
I'm at home in bed with the worst cold.
恐怕我们全家都中招倒下了
Afraid the whole family's down.
恐怕有几棵绿植都倒下了
Might've even lost a few house plants, yeah.
好了 我得休息了
Okay, well, I'm gonna get some rest now.
好的 保重
Alright. Take care.
菲尔
Phil!
你跟我说你把你爸的房车卖掉了
You told me you sold your dad's RV!
你还跟我说你要跑5英里呢
And you told me you were running your 5-mile loop!
这条街在你3英里跑步路线上
This street is on your 3-mile course,
所以你到底是在生谁的气呢 克莱尔
so who are you really mad at, Claire?
歌洛莉亚 我们很抱歉
Gloria, we are so sorry,
但我们没办法去看小乔的演出了
but we're not gonna be able to make it to Joe's play.
不 是因为罗纳多的妈妈 她...
No, no, Ronaldo's mom, she had --
她做了个紧急手术
well, she had emergency surgery,
他和胡娇把他们的大丹犬放到我们家寄养了
and, uh, he and Pepper dropped off their Great Danes
事先完全没通知
to our place with no warning.
不 别碰那个 千万别碰花瓶
No! No, stay away from that! Not the vase!
抱歉 歌洛莉亚 我得先挂了
Sorry, Gloria. I gotta go.
你就不能用患感冒当借口吗
You couldn't just say you had a cold?
是啊 亚伯拉罕·林肯
Oh, yeah, and Abe Lincoln,
他可以简单地说"87年前"
he could've said, "87 years ago,"
哈姆雷特也可以说"不如我自杀算了"
and Hamlet could've said, "Maybe I'll kill myself."
不行 最后的那场收尾戏
No, it's the finishing touches
才是决定作品超凡脱俗的关键 米奇尔
that separate the merely good from great, Mitchell!
亲爱的 我知道你对这事很紧张...
Sweetie, I know you're really tense about this --
别 别说 别乱说招致霉运
No, no, no! Don't jinx it, don't jinx it!
-小卡要去那个大学当主教练... -打住 打住
- Cam is up for head coach at the University of Nor-- - Bup, bup, bup!
打住 打住
Bup, bup!
小卡有可能去中北部密苏里学院
Cam is up for head football coach
当橄榄球主教练
at the University of North Central Missouri.
那是他梦想的工作
It's his dream job,
他们今天会打电话给他告知结果
and they're supposed to call him about it today,
这让他有点疯狂
and it's making him a little crazy.
实际上...
In f-fact --
克莱尔向来都是我爸最爱的孩子
C-Claire's always Dad's favorite,
我对此真的很气愤
and I-I'm really miffed about that.
天啊 又在说这破事啊
Oh, boy. This again, huh?
好了 继续说
Okay. No, go on.
-我准备好了 -我的老天
- I'm ready. - Oh, my God!
-亲爱的 你好美 看看她 -小宝贝
- Honey, you look gorgeous! Look at her. - Ah, sweetie!
我能根据我的初次约会给你点建议吗
Now, may I give you a piece of advice from my first date?
别说你有多想要孩子
Don't say how much you want to have kids,
别哭 你的妆会花掉的
and don't cry, because your makeup will run.
我更担心我的约会对象看到你们俩会夺路而逃
I'm more worried about my date running when he sees you two there.
你们不会注意到我们的存在 好吗
You'll barely even notice us, okay?
做你真实的自我就好 你很风趣幽默的
Just be yourself. You are -- You're so funny.
你可以跟他说那个有趣的故事
Okay, tell that funny story
就是一个老醉汉亲吻驴子的那个
of the old drunk guy who was kissing the donkey.
干嘛扯我家 你的家人就很完美吗
Oh, because your family's perfect?
好了 天啊 来了来了
Okay. Oh, my God! That's it!
工作那边打来的
That's the job!
我的手机在哪儿 我的手机在哪儿
Where's my phone?! Where's my phone?!
这简直是最糟糕的事...
This is the worst thing that could be happ--
好吧 只是我的冥想程序而已
Okay, it's just my mediation app.
好了 你得控制下你男人
Okay, you need to control your man.
如果他今晚收到的是坏消息
If he gets bad news tonight
然后在兰迪面前崩溃了
and melts down in front of Randy,
我就可以跟与他吻别这件事"吻别"了
I can kiss "kssing him goodbye" goodbye.
没事的 有我在呢 我们走吧
Okay, no, I gotcha, I gotcha. Come on, let's go.
我理解我们都会对我们父母的东西
I understand we all get attached to things
有深深的依恋感 不舍得处理掉
that belonged to our parents.
不是这原因
That's not it.
我这么做是为了让你跟我享受一些冒险旅程
I'm doing this so you and I can have some adventures.
难道你看不到 当我们驾车驶过金门大桥时
Can't you see yourself making lists and folding shirts
你在列清单 叠衣服的画面吗
while we drive across the Golden Gate Bridge?
我们永远不会用上这车的
We're never gonna use this thing.
耗油太狠 找个停车的地方要一小时
It guzzles gas, and it takes an hour to park.
那就停在这里吧
Well, then leave it here.
你多年来一直想要一间客房啊
You've always wanted a guest house.
我不要餐桌上还有安全带的客房
Not one with seat belts at the dining table.
没得商量 迪兰
No discussion, Dylan.
我们要带他们去看婴儿心理医生
We're taking them to see a baby psychiatrist.
你还是在纠结那部疯电影吗
Are you still talking about that crazy movie?
孩子的纯洁心灵被毁了
Well, it messed them up!
我们带他们去了公园
We took them to the park.
玩秋千 他们觉得无聊
Swing set -- bored.
看萌萌小松鼠 他们打鼾
Cute squirrels -- snore.
然后有个老太太在遛狗
Then an old lady walking her poodle
绊了一跤 被拖着从玫瑰花丛里穿过
trips and gets dragged through a rosebush,
这两个孩子竟然笑出声
and these two burst out laughing
就像两个玩挠痒痒大战的神经病
like two stoners in a tickle fight.
你们肯定只是反应过度啦
I'm sure you're both overreacting
所有新手爸妈都会这样
the way all new parents do.
不 妈妈 我们要把小孩养坏了
No, Mom, we're screwing this up.
我们最少也需要寻求些帮助
At the very least, we need help,
比如互惠生[一对]保姆之类的
like -- like an au pair or something.
那是两个保姆的意思 对吗
That's two nannies, right?
-正确 -好
- Correct. - Okay.
你们看 他们对那只蝴蝶多温柔呀
Look at how gentle they're being with that butterfly.
看见没 你们只是瞎操心...
See? You two were worrying for no--
-他们把蝴蝶撕碎了 -天啊
- They're tearing it apart. Ohh! - Oh God!
这样好不好 我们把孩子们交给亲家母
What do you say we leave the babies with Farrah
我们几个大人出去边吃晚饭边商量这事
and the grown-ups go out and talk about this over dinner?
好主意
Great idea.
可是有四个人耶
Oh! Four people, though.
普通轿车坐不下呢
Try fitting that in a regular car.
等一下
Wait a minute.
要是我们开那辆房... 你逗我呢吗
What if we took the R-- you kidding me?!
提醒我买些车轮锁啊
Remind me to buy some wheel blocks!
天啊 莉莉需要我帮她一把
Oh, God. Lily needs my help.
你这是在演哪一出
What the hell are you doing?
我提醒她分享那个好笑的驴子故事
I'm -- I'm trying to get her to tell that funny donkey story.
你就学《小熊维尼》里的屹耳驴叫吗
By making an Eeyore sound?
知道吗 不是所有驴子都那么丧的
You know what? Not all donkeys are depressed.
这刻板印象真没礼貌
That's an offensive stereotype
都是一群无知爱荷华州人传的谣言
perpetuated by a bunch of ignorant Iowans.
天啊 我的手机震了
Oh, my God! My phone's buzzing!
原来只是朗吉尼斯
It's just Longinus.
知道了啦 你在网红汉堡店遇到演员玛丽·奥斯蒙了
Yeah, we know. You met Marie Osmond at a Five Guys.
谁在乎啊
Nobody cares.
打住
Stop!
我朋友说我们该尝尝这里的土豆
My friend said we should try the potato.
-莉莉 -同志们 同志们 同志们
- Lily! - Hey, guys. Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
你们好啊 你们怎么来了
Hey, guys! What are you doing here?
休息一下 暂时先不给我们孩子留下童年阴影了
Oh, just taking a break from scarring our children.
别夸张了
Now, come on.
海莉和迪兰有点小崩溃
Haley and Dylan were having a little bit of a meltdown,
我们想着土豆屋不是快停业了吗
and we thought we'd hit Spuds one last time
就抓紧来吃最后一次
before they close for good.
就是啊 真伤感不是吗
I know. It's sad, isn't it?
-我们小时候每年生日都是在这过的 -是啊
- Remember we used to spend all of our birthdays here... - Yeah!
-土豆宝宝霍利会唱给给我们听 -对
- ...and Spuddy Holly would always sing to us. - Yes! Oh.
♪ 加扇贝 去油炸 裹上洋葱 ♪
♪ Scalloped, fried, or lyonnaise ♪
♪ 土豆屋的土豆好吃疯 ♪
♪ Spuds' potatoes amaze ♪
♪ 生日快乐 ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
我想强调一下 我只是被收养的
I want to stress that I'm adopted.
我们要不别打扰那对小情人约会了吧
Why don't we leave the lovebirds to their date?
好主意 但你们知道吗
Good idea, but you know what?
越多人一起分享土豆越美味哦 和坐车一样
Spuds is better with more people, much like a vehicle.
看看他们能否安排我们坐一块吧
Let's -- Let's see if they can sit the rest of us together.
-好啊 -行
- Okay, yeah. - Okay.
好
Alright.
我关注了和小卡竞争教练职位的
I'd been following Cam's competitor for the coaching spot
那人的图享网账号
on Instagram, and --
他打败小卡得到了那份工作
...he beat Cam out for the job,
这代表
which meant, any minute,
小卡随时会得知这令人心碎的消息
Cam would be getting the devastating news himself.
我不能指望靠土豆屋的欢乐气氛
And I-I-I couldn't rely on the joyful environment of Spuds
来缓解这一冲击
to cushion the blow.
但这餐厅有个美名 名主持拉里·金在这
Although, it is famously where Larry King broke up
和四任老婆分的手
with four of his wives.
小卡 小卡
Cam. Cam.
我刚得知一个坏消息
I-I-I just got some bad news,
我想最好是由我来告诉你
and I think it's best that you hear it from me.
我听说了
Oh, I heard.
逆天土豆居然卖光了
They're out of the Impossible Potato.
不好意思
Now, I'm sorry,
你们既然吹嘘这是史上第一款纯肉做的土豆
you advertise the first potato made entirely of meat,
最好就备够所有人的量啊
ya better have enough for everyone.
求你了 快吃药吧
Please just take those pills.
你现在比参加路易斯安那购地案的叛徒
You're more crooked than General James Wilkinson
詹姆斯·威尔金森还坐立不安
during the Louisiana Purchase.
只剩下最后一个州了
We're down to the last state.
我动一下还比较舒服
It's actually better if I move.
这里太美了
Wow. This is gorgeous.
这地方叫什么来着
What do you call this place, again?
珍珠港
Pearl Harbor.
扶好国旗 兄弟们
Save the flag, boys!
海莉 别玩手机了
Haley, get off your phone.
有迪兰妈妈在 他们没事的
The babies are fine with Dylan's mom.
如果你觉得紧张 房车里有我爸的旧足浴盆哦
If you're feeling tense, my dad's old foot bath is in the RV.
就插在车载打火机上
Plugs right into the cigarette lighter.
老公 就算车里有座喷钱的山
Honey, there could be a money volcano
插在白葡萄酒喷泉里
that plugs right into a white wine fountain in there.
我还是不想要那破车
I still wouldn't want it.
我一直想起有些事忘记告诉她了
I keep remembering things I forgot to tell her.
我的小孩已经是反社会了
My kids are already sociopaths.
我不希望他们还因为吃草莓犯过敏
I don't need to give them a strawberry allergy on top of it.
我非常十分完全理解你
Oh, I completely, totally get that.
我要把你电话关了
Just gonna turn this off.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我们都把手机关掉 快点
Hey, let-- let's all turn off our phones. Come on.
-不要 -来嘛 享受当下
- Yeah, you can -- - No, come on. Live in the moment.
此刻多美好啊 我们和家人好友
I mean, appreciate the fact that we live in a town
住在同一个城市
with family and friends
齐聚一堂 这还是...
all sitting at the same table where --
"前总统艾森豪威尔策划诺曼底登陆日入侵"的桌子
oh, yeah, "Eisenhower planned the D-Day invasion."
这八成是假的吧
Well, that's probably not true.
听起来有人为可能要
Sounds like somebody's nervous
搬去密苏里州感到紧张
about a possible move to Missouri.
不 我只是想指出
No, I'm -- I'm just pointing out
这里有很多很棒的人事物
that there are a lot of really great things here.
比如那段萌芽时期的恋情
Like -- Like, wouldn't it be a shame
如果提前结束了 那多可惜啊
to cut that blossoming relationship short?
说真的 我不太信任那个叫兰迪的
Actually, I'm not so sure how much I trust that Randy guy.
什么样的变态才会喜欢12岁小女孩啊
I mean, what kind of sicko is attracted to a 12-year-old?
不知道他父母是不是也教坏他了
I wonder if his parents messed him up, too.
我在一个妈咪博客上看到
You know, I read on a mommy blog
父母失职和孩子日后犯罪有直接联系
that bad parenting is a direct link to future criminality --
还有当DJ
and deejaying.
好了 听我说
Okay, you know what?
你们得当心点
You two need to be careful
你们把时间都花在看育儿文章上
because you can read so much about how to parent,
也许会错过真正教养孩子的机会
you miss out on being one.
米奇尔就曾犯过这种错误
Mitchell struggled with that.
放轻松
Just relax.
小甜心
Aww, sweetheart.
-你给她喷了发胶吗 -一点点
- Did you put hair spray in this? - Just a little bit, yes.
我来放点音乐
I'm gonna put some music on.
-不 小卡 我还要去上班 -跟她跳跳舞
- No, Cam, I have to go work. - Dance with her!
-别 没时间了 -一起摇摆吧
- Come on. I don't have time for this. - Put a little boogie in it.
饶了我吧
No, come on, it--
跳吧 你知道这首歌是你的菜
Just dance. You know you love this song.
那好吧 好吧
Alright. Okay.
谁才是舞后
Who's the dancing queen, huh?
一起摇摆吧
Put a little boogie in it.
看 好玩吧 是不是
See? Fun.
妈呀 撞到她的头了吗
Oh, my -- was that her head?
抱歉 我忘了故事最后是这样的
Sorry. I forgot how that story ended.
最后是我们在急诊室
It ended with us in the ER
那是全世界最好的医院之一
of one of the best hospitals in the world.
距离我们才不到两公里 多好
Nice having that only a mile away.
告诉你 布密苏里的平均寿命
I'll have you know that the life expectancy in Missouri
刚刚超过了阿肯色州和关岛
just climbed above Arkansas and Guam.
把手机还给我 我要订购婴儿头盔
Okay, give me back my phone. I'm ordering baby helmets.
别再担心了
Stop worrying.
孩子们总是磕磕碰碰的
Kids get bonked all the time.
你知道卢克栽过多少跟头吗
Do you know how many tumbles Luke took?
他应该是想出去
I think he wants to go out.
好孩子
Good boy!
聪明的狗狗
Smart dog.
不想扫你的兴 不过这招所有狗都会吧
I hate to break it to you, but I think all dogs can do that.
我要出去玩
I'm gonna play outside.
怎么回事啊
What happened?
他不也很好
And he's fine.
还好
...ish.
我喜欢卢克
I love the guy,
但我们对孩子的期望比他要高一些
but we're aiming a little bit higher than Luke.
海莉 其实孩子们偶尔受点小伤是好事
Haley, you kind of want your kids to get knocked around a little.
能让他们更坚强地
It toughens them up for things
面对成年人都会经历的事
that we all go through in adulthood.
老爸赢了
Daddy wins!
相信奇迹吗
Do you believe in miracles?!
美利坚万岁 美利
Usa! Us--
不
Oh, no!
上帝啊
Oh, geez!
天啊 刚刚那是什么
Oh, my -- What was that?
-是个人吗 -我没事
- Was that a person that fell -- - I'm good!
爸爸
Dad?!
老爸 接招
Hey, Dad, think fast.
你是不是有点儿过于
Aren't you being a little --
哪有什么不测
But this isn't an emergen--
现在有了
Now it I-I-I-I-is!
确实 我已经尝不出咸味了 不过
I mean, sure, I can no longer taste salt, but --
我知道他们会有磕磕碰碰
I know that they're going to get bumps and bruises,
但我指的是心灵创伤
but I'm talking about psychological scars.
我自己就有过那种经历
I've had some experience with that myself.
惊喜啊啊啊
Surpri--
不
No!
不 不
No! No!
对不起
I'm sorry!
什么都没发生
Nothing's happening!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
她至今仍很受伤
It still haunts her.
听了别尴尬 不过她至今
Not to be weird, but she still won't let me
都不让我在做爱时提你们的名字
mention your names while we're making love.
好吧
Okay.
瞧瞧啊
Well, well, well.
是的 瞧瞧啊
Yes, well, well, well.
看来你的感冒好多了
I see your cold is better.
后来发现我只是有一点过敏啦
Turns out it was, like, an allergy...thing.
胡娇的大丹狗呢
And Pepper's Great Danes?
你知道 它们是大型犬
Oh, uh, well, you know, they're big dogs.
它们没有那么长的寿命
They -- Um, and they don't, uh, uh, live long.
所以它们
So they're --
它们死了
they're dead.
你一定以为我是弗雷德里克·苏厄德
I must look like Frederick Seward
在收购阿拉斯加
during the Alaska Purchase,
显然你以为你怎么忽悠我都会买单
because, apparently, you think that I'll buy anything.
歌洛莉亚 好吧
Gloria, okay, okay.
抱歉 抱歉我们对你说谎了
We're s-we're sorry-we're sorry we lied to you,
但假如这能让你感觉好些
but if it makes you feel any better,
朗吉尼斯给你拍了一张很美的照片
Longinus took this really great photo of you
就是你去夏奇拉演唱会那晚
at the Shakira concert the night
你得了红眼病不能去莉莉的单簧管独奏会
that you missed Lily's clarinet recital because of pink eye.
看来你一直在等着对我会心一击
I see that you've been waiting to spring that attack on me,
像新奥尔良战役中的安德鲁·杰克逊那样
just like Andrew Jackson in the Battle of New Orleans.
我得一直听她这么说话了吗
Is this my life now?
我去趟卫生间
I'm gonna use the restroom.
你们赶紧点个桌边烤土豆
Will someone order the table-side baked potatoes?
来这吃的一半原因就是为了看烤土豆表演
I mean, that's half of why you come here -- for the show.
公共厕所
Public restroom, huh?
真可惜他不能去自己车里解决私人问题
Shame he can't go in the privacy of his own car.
确实 房车里确实有卫生间
It's true. The RV does have a bathroom.
还有嵌死的咖啡机
And a bolted-down Mr. Coffee,
防熊的底盘食品箱
bear-proof undercarriage food bins.
你觉得车已经跑过多少公里了
And how many miles would you say is on it?
等等
Wait!
你居然要把她在同城网站上卖掉
You're selling her on Craigslist?
甚至用的照片还很难看
And this isn't even a good picture!
她这一面不上相
This is her bad side!
我懂房车的价值 克莱尔
Hey, look, I get the value of an RV, Claire.
加州有那么多自然美景值得探索
There is so much natural beauty to explore here in California.
黄金之州
The Golden State!
你不是真的想反悔搬去密苏里吧
Are you really trying to get out of moving to Missouri?
不是
No, no!
听起来我们需要密苏里妥协案
Sounds like what we need is a Missouri Compromise.
歌洛莉亚 你在给外公的土豆蒂尼下药吗
Gloria, are you drugging Grandpa's Potato-tini?
你也看到他腰都直不起来了
You saw how bent over he is.
不知道为什么 他很怕吃药
For some reason, he's scared of pills,
我不能再看着他疼下去了
and I can't watch him suffer anymore.
我真讨厌餐厅用可爱的卫生间标识
I hate it when they get cute with the bathroom signs.
为什么薯条代表女士
Why would French fries mean ladies
烤土豆代表男士
and baked potato gents?
给其中一个小人加条裙子不就得了
Just throw one of them into a skirt.
爸
So, uh, Dad,
歌洛莉亚说你不肯吃背痛药
Gloria says that you won't take pills for your back?
现在人人都要说我了吗
I got to get this from all sides now?
我不喜欢那些药给我的影响 行吗
I don't like what they do to me, alright?
它们让我觉得特别
They make me feel super...
饥渴 便秘
Horny? Constipated?
情绪化
Emotional.
有时你忍一忍就过去了 但这次要命了
You know, sometimes you can just ride out a pause, buddy.
实在是太痛 我忍不住了
Anyway, the pain got so bad, I broke down.
就在卫生间吃了两片药
I took a couple in the men's room,
已经到了最大剂量 所以准备好啦
which is the maximum dose, so strap in.
不
N-n--
我会怀念这个地方的
You know, I'm gonna miss this place.
看 土豆宝宝霍利
Look, Spuddy Holly!
他就要唱这些了 对吧
He just about said it all, didn't he?
♪ 加扇贝 去油炸 裹上洋葱 ♪
♪ Scalloped, fried, lyonnaise. ♪
♪ 土豆屋的土豆好吃疯 ♪
♪ Spuds' potatoes amaze ♪
四片 他没事吧
Four pills? Is he gonna be okay?
他没事的
He can handle it.
爸爸可是从八十年代的衣柜界活下来了
Dad lived through the closet scene in the '80s.
我也是
So did I.
天啊 他在和莉莉和迪兰说话
Oh, my God. He's talking to Lily and Dylan!
我才是迪兰
I'm Dylan.
兰迪 你让我想起了年轻时的我
You know, Randy, you remind me of a young me,
和一位越南美女在胡志明市游荡
prowling Saigon with a Vietnamese beauty.
-我常去一个酒吧 -我们走吧
- There was this one bar I used to -- - Let's go.
给你弄点黑咖啡喝
Let's get you some black coffee.
躲猫猫啦 乔治 茵素
Peekaboo! George! Poppy!
有人在家吗
Hello? Is anybody home?
怎么回事 纸巾先生通常都能逗笑他们啊
What gives? Mister Napkin usually kills.
谁要咖啡
Who wanted coffee?
这
Ah, here!
他们笑了 看到吗 他们有病
They're laughing! See? They're psychos!
对不起 先生 你还好吗
Ay! Sorry, mister. Are you okay?
我没一点感觉 更吓人了
I actually don't feel anything, which is even more scary.
去感觉 别害怕 小家伙
Don't be scared to feel, buddy.
你最后可能会逃离
You could end up running away
你孩子的情绪发作
from an emotional situation with your kids,
但解开孩子情绪的结是最值的
and those are always the most rewarding.
要我说 你很幸运
You ask me, you're lucky.
她发短信甩我的
She dumped me by text
当时还在和她年长的男友热吻
while making out with her old boyfriend.
我崩溃哭泣
I broke down crying.
炭笔条花得跟睫毛膏一样
My charcoal ran like mascara.
还得靠另一队的吉利物安慰我来着
I had to be comforted by the other team's mascot.
这是幸运吗
Lucky?
我不会骗你
Aw, I'm not gonna lie to you.
这很糟糕
It sucks,
有时候糟糕的感觉还会持续一阵子
and sometimes it's got to suck for a while.
我真希望我可以说出什么咒语
I just wish I could say some magic words
或是拥抱你 就让这感觉烟消云散
or give you a hug, make it all go away.
某种程度上 是他培育我成长
In a way, he raised me.
你振作点行不行啊 老爸
Pull yourself together, man!
海莉
Haley, um,
我想你药物导致变正常人的外公
I think what your... chemically humanized grandfather
想说的是 孩子天生就是生存者
is trying to say is that kids are built to last.
的确 他们会碰到许多磨难
Sure, they -- they go through stuff,
但雨过就会天晴 特别是有你们在身边帮忙
but they survive, especially when you're around to help.
我想念他
I miss him.
我知道
Yeah.
他是你第一个真正意义上的男朋友
He was your first real boyfriend.
我一直希望他能出现
I keep expecting him to show up.
他以前都是晚上过来 我会偷偷溜出去看他
He used to come by at night, and I'd sneak out to see him.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你知道吗
You knew?
他开一辆没有消音器的三十年前的旧车
His car is 30 years old and doesn't have a muffler.
他居然还按喇叭
And he honked.
我超爱那台车
I loved that car.
我知道你现在很难过 宝贝
I know it hurts now, sweetheart,
但这样你才明白这段感情是值得拥有的
but that's how you know it was a relationship worth having.
后来呢
Well, what happened?
他回来了吗
Did he come back?
那
That --
那就是你 老兄
That was you, buddy.
我喜欢这个孩子
I love this kid.
我记得他还是个宝宝的时候
I remember when he was a baby.
咱们第一次见时我上高中
We met my senior year of high school.
大家到底以为我是谁啊
Who does everyone think I am?
你知道
You know, it's --
有关宝宝 你爱上一个宝宝
Thing about babies, you -- you fall in love with a baby
胖嘟嘟超级可爱
with the cutest little fat folds,
然后 突然 他们就离开了
and then -- bam -- they're gone.
但没事 因为取而代之的
But it's okay, because in its place
是个学步的娃娃
is this...toddler
拥有世上最美好的笑声
with the greatest laugh on Earth.
然后又一天 这个娃娃也不见了
And then one day, the toddler's gone,
取代的 是一个小孩子
and in its place, a little kid
他会问你听过的最有趣的问题
that asks the most interesting questions you've ever heard.
就一直这样子
And this keeps going on like that,
但你从没有错过他们的机会
but you never get the chance to miss any of them,
因为总会有一个新的孩子取代之前那个
'cause there's always a new kid to take the place of the old.
直到他们长大
Until they grow up.
然后 突然
And then...in a moment,
所有这些你爱上的孩子们
all those kids you fell in love with
同时走出了家门
walk out the door at the same time.
天啊
Jesus.
我不是故意扫兴
Oh, I don't mean to be a bummer.
我只是说 时光飞逝
I'm just saying it goes fast.
就像老话说的
Like the expression...
"你永远不知道最后一次抱起自己孩子是什么时候"
"You never know the last time you pick up your kid."
海莉 我们要说的是
The point we're making, Haley,
担心自己的孩子很正常
is that it's natural to worry over your kids.
说明你爱他们
It -- It just means that you love them.
所以我一直会感觉我把他们养坏了
So, I'm always gonna feel like I screwed them up somehow?
差不多
Kind of.
但最终你能够一笑而过
I mean, eventually, you'll be able to laugh at it --
大概是你向自己孩子保证
probably around the time that you're reassuring your own children
他们没有养坏他们宝宝的时候吧
that they didn't screw up their babies.
谢谢啦
Thanks.
不 谢谢你
No, actually, thank you.
作为父母 我们很高兴知道我们仍有
It's nice to know, as parents, that we can still have --
爸爸
Dad?
我想念抱起我的小女儿
I miss picking up my little girl.
不会是最后一次的 可恶
And it won't be the last time, damn it!
你想要我骑在我肩上吗 宝贝
Oh! You want a piggyback ride, honey?
不不不
No. No. No.
-你确定 -好了 到此为止
- You sure? - Okay, I'm calling it.
天啊
Oh, my gosh!
好了 终于来了
Okay, this is it!
你好
Hello?
-炸薯条味道很普通啊 -抱歉
- The French fries were only okay. - Sorry about that.
花了点时间才把杰弄上车
Took a minute getting Jay to his car. Mm.
他看到一片形状与他以前橄榄球教练相似的云
He saw a cloud that looked like his old football coach,
然后他不想自己待着
and he didn't want to be alone.
-今晚意外地挺耐人寻味的啊 -是啊
- Turned out to be kind of a fun night, huh? - Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
对了
By the way...
我在网上贴的广告收到回复啦
I got a response to my Craigslist ad.
那好快啊
Oh. Oh, that was fast.
是的
Yeah.
一对人很好的夫妇
Yeah, really nice couple,
很快要成为空巢老人
soon to be empty nesters --
有3个孩子 2个新生的外孙
three kids, two new grandkids.
老婆有点神经兮兮
Wife's a little high-strung.
老公有点古里古怪
Husband's a bit of an oddball
而且对生活十分有激情
with an infectious lust for life.
他们听起来好奇怪啊 不卖
They sound like weirdos. No sale.
菲尔 我是在说我们俩
Phil, I'm talking about us.
我们应该把房车留下
We should keep the RV.
这主意真是太棒了
That is amazing.
是什么让你改变了心意
What changed your mind?
我想应该是因为今晚听到的那些故事吧
I think it was hearing all those stories tonight.
孩子们很快就会离我们而去
And the kids'll be gone soon.
我们估计会花很多时间在旅游上
We'll probably spend a lot of time on the road.
反正都要出游 何不在极尽奢华
Might as well do it in the height of luxury --
带地毯洗手间与四合一游戏桌的车上游呢
with a carpeted bathroom and a four-in-one game table.
你真是太棒了
You're incredible.
我是做了什么好事才能够有你这样的贤妻
What did I do to deserve a wife cool enough
让我留下我爸的房车以及他的新生鹦鹉
to let me keep my dad's RV and his newborn parrot?
他的新生什么
His newborn what?
亲爱的 鹦鹉的寿命可以到70至8...
Honey, parrots live like 70 to 8-- Mmmmmm.
完全没想到会接到的电话啊
That was not the call I was expecting.
亲爱的 我懂
Sweetie, I know.
我看到另一个教练在网上发庆祝的照片了
I-I saw the other coach celebrating on Instagram,
浑身都倒了运动饮料 还是在房子里
uh, drenching himself in Gatorade -- in the house.
还有地毯呢 谁来清理呢
There was a rug. Who's gonna clean that up?
我猜肯定不是他来清理
Not him, I bet.
从你的表情来看
I'm reading from your face
我跟你说之前你是不知道这事的
that you didn't know until I just told you.
我现在是紧张所以说个不停
Now I'm just talking out of nerves.
妈的 我...
Damn it! I --
我没被选吗
I didn't get it?!
我知道我喜怒不形于色 但我超想要这工作
I mean, I know I'm hard to read, but I really wanted that job.
我很遗憾 来抱抱
I'm so sorry. C-Come here.
等等 所以你才整晚不停跟我说
Wait, is that why you were selling California
加州的各种好吗
all night long to me?
因为你希望我知道时不会太难过
Because you wanted to soften the blow when I heard?
真是又怪又有点甜
Well, that is weirdly sweet.
-我很快就过来 -好
- I'll be there in a second. - Okay.
我想跟你们说驴子的故事超成功
Um... Just wanted to let you know the donkey story killed.
-哈哈 -一下让场面不再尴尬
- Ha ha! - It totally broke the ice.
我们聊得非常开心
We've been having so much fun!
宝贝 我好为你开心
Oh, honey! I'm so happy!
谢谢 我也很开心
Thanks. Me, too.
他问我能不能去外面一起吃个冰激凌
He asked if I could go outside and get ice cream.
我可以去吗
Can I?
当然啦 没问题
O-Of course, yes.
但选择配料时要非常谨慎
But just make good choices about the toppings.
不要加糖屑 那是蜡做的垃圾
Don't get sprinkles. They're just wax.
至少我们也获得了一个小胜利不是吗
Well, now, there's a small victory at least, right?
初次约会大成功 我们也得到了一次助攻
First date was a success, and we get an assist.
抱歉 我用了橄榄球的术语
S-- Uh, sorry -- football term.
并不是好吗
Eh, except it isn't.
对了 你接到的电话是谁打来的
Uh, by the way, what was that phone call you got?
简直要疯
Oh. Uh crazy.
是我们的领养中介
Our adoption agency.
很多年以前的那个吗
From years ago?
对啊 他们最近在搬移数据库
Y-Yeah, apparently, uh, they were migrating the database,
我们的档案意外被重启了 然后呢...
and somehow, our profile got accidentally reactivated and --
有人选了我们
and somebody picked us.
等等 选我们
Wait, picked us?
是指给我们小宝宝吗
A-As in there-- there's a baby?
对啊 是不是太疯狂了
I know. Wild, right?
那你... 你拒绝他们了吧
W-Well, you -- you told them no?
我觉得不跟你说就拒绝不太好
Well, it felt wrong until I talked to you about it,
但 我... 我会
but, yeah, I-I'll -- I will.
我会跟他们说的
I'll tell 'em.
今晚说那些故事真是很有趣呢
It was really fun telling those stories tonight.
对啊
Yeah.
让我换了一个角度来看待失去工作这件事
Really puts losing a job in perspective.
我们人生最好的那些回忆
You know, none of our best memories
跟工作完全没有任何关系
have anything to do with work.
反而全都是跟外面那个小姑娘有关
They all have to do with that little girl right out there.
你知道其实她也已经不小了吧
Well, you know, she's not so little anymore.
感觉牵手的时刻要到了
Oh. Oh, I think we're about to have a hand-holding moment.
我们这些年来对养孩子也十分有心得了吧
You know, we got pretty good at this parenting thing,
你觉得呢
didn't we?
我们今晚就得回复那个中介吗
so, uh, we -- we have to tell the agency tonight?
我们应该有24小时的时间可以做决定
Well, technically, we have 24 hours to, uh...decide.
好的
Okay.
杰
Jay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我以后不会再给你下药了
I will never drug you again.
但是看到你吐露心事与诚实真的很好呢
But it was so nice to see you so open and honest.
我也当了一回"正直的亚伯"了
Yeah, I was a regular "Honest Abe."
那是谁啊
Who's that?
偶尔释放一下感情或许也是件好事吧
It's probably good to be emotional every now and then.
或许我该练习练习不吃药就能做到那样
I should probably practice letting it out without a pill.
我很为你的表演感到骄傲呢
Hey, I was proud of you in that show you did.
我爱你
I love you!
我知道 同样的对话我们昨晚说过四次了
I know. We had this conversation four times last night.
真的吗
Really?
或许你该检查一下你都打给谁过
Um, maybe you should check your call history.
别啊
Oh, no.
你激励了我
You inspire me.
菲尔 或许就是因为那样
And I think I'm rude to you sometimes
所以我有时候会故意对你不太有礼
because I'm scared of that, Phil.
这是我绕着弯在说
This is a long way of saying
我想我终于有了最好的死党
I think I finally have a best friend.
你激励了我
You inspire me.
菲尔 或许就是因为那样
And I think I'm rude to you sometimes